

Tomas Silny

Fullstack Developer

M. R. Stefanika 41, Cifer, Slovakia +421 904 102 216 · tomas.silny7@gmail.com

GitHub, My portfolio

Date / Place of birth 04/20/1999, Trnava, Slovakia, Europe

Nationality

Slovak

Skills
React, React Native, NextJS
JavaScript
HTML & CSS
C#/.NET
Java
PHP, Laravel
Git
SQL
Python
С
Computer Networking
Node.js
Languages Slovak
English (B2)

Profile

Experienced Fullstack Software Developer with more than 4 years of experience in Web & Mobile Development using the latest technologies. I have experience working either in a company or as a freelancer as well. I have a decent knowledge of MVC architecture, REST-based Web Services, JavaScript frameworks with different UI libraries and packages, relational database systems, multiplatform mobile app development (Android & iOS), computer networks, and desktop app development. I'm reliable, can learn quickly, and take care of every detail.

Employment History

Fullstack Developer, Softlogic Software

January 2022 — Present (softlogicsoftware.com, freelancing, my website)

- Development of Web and Mobile apps for customers and companies
- Solved complex problems using the latest technologies such as React, Laravel, NextJS, Expo, and cloud services
- Coded software updates and maintained already developed systems
- Communicated with the customers and wrote documentations and user manuals

Fullstack Developer, SensoHealth Solutions s.r.o.

December 2019 — January 2022 (sensohealth.org)

- The company is focused on research in human body motion using special 3D cameras - Gait and Posture analysis.
- Designed and developed a UI using React, NextJS, React Native, and WPF
- Used Laravel Framework and C# as a backend running on Azure services
- Developed communication through TCP among hardware devices
- Coded software updates, designed new functions, wrote documentation
- Managed a small team of developers
- Worked close with the CEO

Education

MSc. in Project Management, EDU Effective Business School, Prague, **Czech Republic**

November 2021 – September 2022

Bachelor of Computer Science, Matej Bel University, Banska Bystrica, Slovakia

September 2018 — June 2021

Courses

Programming in C language, IT Learning Slovakia

February 2018 — March 2018

CISCO CCNA 1 & 2, CISCO NETACAD

November 2016 - December 2017

Extra-curricular activities

1st place at Young Computer Scientist competition, University of Economics, Bratislava, Slovakia

April 2018

Developed an app for scanning dangerous products on the market.
Source code available on my GitHub (tomassilny)

Junior Internet competition Slovakia, Slovak Technical University, Bratislava, Slovakia

February 2017

 Price of Dean of the Slovak Technical University, Bratislava for app helping our environment. Source code available on my GitHub (tomassilny)

Portfolio

ByteShare.net, Web Development

September 2021 — Present

- File manager that allows to upload large files including remote upload from any URL or via FTP and with my own built API
- Built using Laravel, Python, Bootstrap and JavaScript
- Used by thousands of people worldwide

CodeDocs.org, Web Development

March 2021 — April 2021

- Website generated using Wikipedia API. This includes more than 5000 generated pages about software development and IT.
- Built using HTML & CSS, PHP, JavaScript and MySQL.

Please visit my online interactive portfolio at: <u>tomassilny.github.io</u> for more references